State University of New York, Board of Trustees; Records apap098
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
State University of New York Board of Trustees Records
1948-2001
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
apap098
7.22 cubic ft. processed to date
State University of New York (SUNY) Board of Trustees Records document the activities of public higher education campuses across New York State, during the later half of the twentieth century.
Access
Access to this record group is unrestricted.
Acquisition Information
All items in this manuscript group were donated to the University Libraries, M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections and Archives.
Organizational Sketch
Created in 1948 with the founding of the State University of New York (SUNY), the SUNY Board of Trustees is responsible for the overall central administration, supervision, and coordination of these state-operated institutions. The central administration has its headquarters in Albany, New York.
Scope and Contents
An artificial collection of official records of the State University of New York (SUNY). SUNY is a statewide system of higher education established under Gov. Thomas E. Dewey in 1948. The collection includes system-wide planning documents, reports, and other official publications (principally, News), and selected Board of Trustees minutes; internal draft copies of the Board of Trustees minutes are also present in the collection. Also, materials of note include newspaper clippings related to SUNY, Student Association of the State University of New York (SASU) correspondence, and financial information pertaining to the SUNY system budget.
The records of the Office of the President (UA-000) include summary minutes of the SUNY Board of Trustees meetings for 1968, 1970-1984. Related collections include: the papers of Donald Blinken (APAP-080) and the records of the State University Construction (APAP-097) and the records of the State University of New York, University Faculty Senate (APAP-093) and the records of the Student Association of the State University of New York (SASU) (APAP-046).
Arrangement of the Collection
The collection is organized into the following series:
Series 1: Administrative Files, 1960-1982
Series 2: Subject Files, 1948-2001
Series 1 and 2 are arranged alphabetically.
Higher education and state--New York (State); Higher education and state--New York (State)--History--20th century; College students--New York (State); Minutes; Correspondence; Education; State University of New York SUNY, Central Administration; Student Association of the State University of New York; State University of New York, Board of Trustees
- Administrative Files, 1960-1982; 3.42 cubic ft.
  Arrangement
  Arranged alphabetically.
  Scope and Contents
  Series 1 consists of correspondence from the office of the Chancellor, the Board of Trustees, and drafts of Board of Trustees meeting minutes. Correspondence from various offices in the central administrative office, from SUNY schools are also present. Materials of note also include reports created by the central administrative office and policy statements.
  - "A Report on the Future of Campus Schools", 1975 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Agenda – State University of New York Meeting of the Board of Trustees – November 27th, 1978 [1 of 2] (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Agenda – State University of New York Meeting of the Board of Trustees – November 27th, 1978 [2 of 2] (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Assembly of the State of New York Correspondence, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Association of Colleges and Universities of the State of New York Correspondence, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - "Basic Guidelines: Preparation of Campus Master Plans", Undated (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Board of Trustees Correspondence, 1969-1971; 1973-1974 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Board of Trustees Correspondence, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Board of Trustees Correspondence, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Board of Trustees Correspondence, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Board of Trustees Correspondence, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Board of Trustees Correspondence, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Board of Trustees Correspondence, 1980-1981; Undated (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Board of Trustees Meeting Minutes, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Board of Trustees Meeting Minutes, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Board of Trustees Meeting Minutes, 1970-1972 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Board of Trustees Meeting Minutes, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Board of Trustees Meeting Minutes, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Board of Trustees Meeting Minutes, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Board of Trustees Meeting Minutes [1 of 2], 1976 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Board of Trustees Meeting Minutes [2 of 2], 1976 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Board of Trustees Meeting Minutes, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Board of Trustees Meeting Minutes, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Board of Trustees Meeting Minutes [1 of 2], 1979 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Board of Trustees Meeting Minutes [2 of 2], 1979 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Board of Trustees Meeting Minutes, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Board of Trustees Meeting Minutes, 1981; Undated (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Board of Trustees Resolutions, 1972; 1979; Undated (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Chancellor Clifton R. Wharton Jr. Calendar, 1979 June (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Chancellor Clifton R. Wharton Jr. Correspondence [1 of 4], 1978 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Chancellor Clifton R. Wharton Jr. Correspondence [2 of 4], 1978 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Chancellor Clifton R. Wharton Jr. Correspondence [3 of 4], 1978 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Chancellor Clifton R. Wharton Jr. Correspondence [4 of 4], 1978 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Chancellor Clifton R. Wharton Jr. Correspondence [1 of 5], 1979 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Chancellor Clifton R. Wharton Jr. Correspondence [2 of 5], 1979 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Chancellor Clifton R. Wharton Jr. Correspondence [3 of 5], 1979 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Chancellor Clifton R. Wharton Jr. Correspondence [4 of 5], 1979 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Chancellor Clifton R. Wharton Jr. Correspondence [5 of 5], 1979 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Chancellor Clifton R. Wharton Jr. Correspondence [1 of 5], 1980 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Chancellor Clifton R. Wharton Jr. Correspondence [2 of 5], 1980 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Chancellor Clifton R. Wharton Jr. Correspondence [3 of 5], 1980 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Chancellor Clifton R. Wharton Jr. Correspondence [4 of 5], 1980 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Chancellor Clifton R. Wharton Jr. Correspondence [5 of 5], 1980 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Chancellor Clifton R. Wharton Jr. Correspondence, 1981-1982; Undated (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Chancellor Ernest L. Boyer Correspondence, 1971-1973 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Chancellor Ernest L. Boyer Correspondence [1 of 4], 1974 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Chancellor Ernest L. Boyer Correspondence [2 of 4], 1974 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Chancellor Ernest L. Boyer Correspondence [3 of 4], 1974 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Chancellor Ernest L. Boyer Correspondence [4 of 4], 1974 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Chancellor Ernest L. Boyer Correspondence [1 of 4], 1975 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Chancellor Ernest L. Boyer Correspondence [2 of 4], 1975 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Chancellor Ernest L. Boyer Correspondence [3 of 4], 1975 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Chancellor Ernest L. Boyer Correspondence [4 of 4], 1975 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Chancellor Ernest L. Boyer Correspondence [1 of 4], 1976 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Chancellor Ernest L. Boyer Correspondence [2 of 4], 1976 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Chancellor Ernest L. Boyer Correspondence [3 of 4], 1976 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Chancellor Ernest L. Boyer Correspondence [4 of 4], 1976 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Chancellor Ernest L. Boyer Correspondence, 1977; Undated (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Chancellor Ernest L. Boyer Press Conference Regarding SUNY Construction Moratorium and Enrollment Freeze, 1979 November (Reel 1)
  - Chancellor James F. Kelly Correspondence, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Chancellor James F. Kelly Correspondence [1 of 2], 1977 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Chancellor James F. Kelly Correspondence [2 of 2], 1977 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Chancellor Samuel B. Gould Correspondence, 1967; 1970 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Chief Business Officers, State Operated Campuses Correspondence, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Council of Presidents Agenda, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - CUNY Correspondence, 1975; 1981 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Deputy to the Chancellor Correspondence, 1975-1976; 1979; Undated (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Executive Chamber; Hugh L. Carey, Governor Correspondence, 1979-1980 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Information on SUNY System [1 of 2], 1978-1981 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Information on SUNY System [2 of 2], 1978-1981 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Investment Policy and Social Concerns, 1978-1979; Undated (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Litigation Reports, 1980-1981 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Memorandum in Support of Proposal to Add Students to Governing Board, Undated (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Memorandum to Presidents, 1974-1979 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Monthly Report, 1979-1980 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Monthly Report of Campus Activities, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - National Institute of Education Correspondence, Undated (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - News Release, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Notes on Activity Fees, 1975; Undated (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Policy Statement Governing All University Based and Sponsored Activities, Undated (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - President's Commission on White House Fellowships Correspondence, Undated (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Residence Hall Budget Correspondence, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Senate of New York Correspondence, 1976; 1980 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - State Education Department Correspondence, 1978-1979 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Statement of the Board of Trustees on Co-Location, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - SUNY Albany President Correspondence, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - SUNY Associate Chancellor for Community Colleges Correspondence, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - SUNY Associate Chancellor for Policy and Planning Correspondence, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - SUNY Binghamton Department of Chemistry Correspondence, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - SUNY Binghamton President Correspondence, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - SUNY Buffalo Student Association Correspondence, 1974; 1977; 1980; Undated (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - SUNY Buffalo Vice President for Finance and Management Correspondence, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - SUNY Buffalo Vice President for Health Services Correspondence, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - SUNY Director of Administrative Services Correspondence, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - SUNY Executive Vice Chancellor Correspondence, 1974-1975 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - SUNY General Manager for Central Administration Services Correspondence, 1976-1978 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - SUNY Liaison Officers Correspondence, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - SUNY Office of Institutional Research and Analytical Studies Correspondence, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - SUNY Office of the University Counsel and Vice Chancellor of Legal Affairs Correspondence, 1975; 1977; 1980 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - SUNY Office of University Financial Analysis Correspondence, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - SUNY Student Assembly Correspondence, 1974-1978; Undated (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - SUNY Vice Chancellor for Academic Policy Correspondence, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - SUNY Vice Chancellor for Academic Programs Correspondence, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - SUNY Vice Chancellor for Academic Programs, Policy and Planning Correspondence, 1979-1980 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - SUNY Vice Chancellor for Educational Services Correspondence, 1978-1980 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - SUNY Vice Chancellor for Faculty and Staff Relations Correspondence, 1980-1981 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - SUNY Vice Chancellor for Finance and Business Correspondence, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - SUNY Vice Chancellor for University Affairs Correspondence, 1973-1977 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - SUNY Vice Chancellor for University-Wide Activities Correspondence, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - SUNY Vice Chancellor for University-Wide Services and Special Programs Correspondence, 1975; Undated (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - U.S. House of Representatives Correspondence, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 41)
- Subject Files, 1948-2001; 3.80 cubic ft.
  Series 2 consists of publications from SUNY, including various newsletters, published meeting minutes, and annual reports. Also included in Subject Files is correspondence from various educational organizations outside of the SUNY system, papers from the SASU, and studies regarding higher education systems in New York and across the country.
  - 15th Annual Meeting of the American Association of State Colleges and Universities, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - 1974 Pilot Program to Bring 500 German Students to Colleges in US, Undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - 1974-1975 SUNY Academic Calendar, Undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - ACMCT – Association of Council Members and College Trustees of the State University of New York, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Affirmative Action Search Waivers, Undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Application Submitted to the National Science Foundation, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Association of Council Members and College Trustees, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Association of Councils and Board of Trustees Conference/Convention, Undated (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Association of Illinois Student Governments Newsletter, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Associations of Campus-Related Foundations Meeting with Board of Trustees, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Auxiliary Services, 1973-1976 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Auxiliary Services, Undated (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Biographical Information on Board of Trustees Members and SUNY Chancellors, Undated (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Confederation of Alumni Associations, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Council of Chief State School Officers, Undated (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Demographic Distribution by County of Students Attending Various SUNY Universities and Specialized Colleges, Undated (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - "Discrimination Against Women in Higher Education – and Afterward", Undated (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Dr. Charles W. Laffin Review, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Education Laws, 1971-1976; 1979-1980; Undated (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Eleven Years of Progress in Special Programs of State University of New York, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - EOP in SUNY Schools, 1976; 1978; 1980 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Experimental Program for Opportunities in Advance Study and Research in Education, Undated (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - The Federal Education Project Newsletter, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Final Report – State University Trustee Committee on the Special Problems of the Community Colleges, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Guidelines for Development of the Campus Instructional Calendar, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Guidelines for Presidents Resuming Full-Time Faculty Status, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Guidelines for the Review Process for the Presidents and Chancellors, 1973; 1979; 1981 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Guidelines for 1978-1979 Discretionary Increases to Academic and Professional Employees, Undated (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Handwritten Notes, Undated (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - "First Impressions and Next Steps", 1980 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Interim Guidelines for Implementation of the SUNY Transfer Policy, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Intern Program Reference Materials, Undated (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - International Programs Quarterly, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Investment Needs Model, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Kings College, Undated (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Legislative Memo, Undated (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Minority Discrimination and the Future of Asian Studies in the United States, 1977; Undated (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - The National Association of State Universities and Land-Grant Colleges, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - National Student Lobby, Undated (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - The New Boom in Career Education – A Skeptic's View, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - New York Public Interest Research Group, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - New York State Civil Service Commission, Undated (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1971-1974; 1976-1977; 1979-1980; Undated (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - NYSED – New York State Department of Education Memos and News, 1973; 1979 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Panel Discussion: The University's Search for Knowledge, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Panel on Faculty Review, 1975-1976 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - People of the State of New York v. The Trustees of the State University of New York, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Perspectives on Trusteeship – Association of Governing Boards of Universities and Colleges, Undated (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Policies of the Board of Trustees, 1954-1956; 1959; 1961-1962; 1964-1966 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Policies of the Board of Trustees, 1967-1968; 1970-1974 (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Policies of the Board of Trustees, 1975-1977; 1980-1981 (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Policies of the Board of Trustees, 1983; 1987; 1989-1990 (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Policies of the Board of Trustees, 1992-1994; 2001; Undated (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Policy Boards and Student Participation, 1970; 1972; 1974 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Portrait of the Defaulter as a Win Warrior, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Position and Funding Reductions, Undated (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Possible Standing Meeting Agenda, Undated (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Poster – Why We Should Egg the Trustees, Undated (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Presidents Inauguration Addresses, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Program for Enhanced Management Effectiveness, Undated (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Projected Full-Time Undergraduate Enrollments for New York State Through 1990, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Public Higher Education – Can We Afford to Live Without It?, Undated (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Published Board of Trustees Meeting Minutes, 1948-1949 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Published Board of Trustees Meeting Minutes, 1950 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Published Board of Trustees Meeting Minutes, 1951-1952 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Published Board of Trustees Meeting Minutes, 1953-1954 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Published Board of Trustees Meeting Minutes, 1955-1956 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Published Board of Trustees Meeting Minutes, 1957-1958 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Published Board of Trustees Meeting Minutes, 1959-1960 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Published Board of Trustees Meeting Minutes, 1961-1962 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Published Board of Trustees Meeting Minutes, 1963-1964 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Published Board of Trustees Meeting Minutes, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Published Board of Trustees Meeting Minutes, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Published Board of Trustees Meeting Minutes, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Regulations and Procedures for Maintaining Public Order on Campuses of the State University of New York, (State University College at Oswego), Undated (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Regulations Governing the Possession, Storage, Care and Use of Firearms on State-Operated Campuses, Undated (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - SASU – Student Association of the State University, 1971-1976; Undated (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Schenectady County Community College – Annual Report of the President, 1977-1978 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Seventh Annual Conference on the Leadership of the Trustee, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Short History of the Proposed Attendance Policy, Undated (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Some Psychological Considerations in Faculty Evaluations, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - State University College, Potsdam – President's Annual Report, 1977-1978 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - State University Newsletter, 1958-1959 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - State University Newsletter, 1960-1961 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - State University Newsletter, 1962-1963 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - State University Newsletter, 1964-1965 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - State University Newsletter, 1966-1967 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - State University Newsletter, 1968-1969 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - State University of New York Annual Report, 1949-1952 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - State University of New York Annual Report, 1954; 1956 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - State University of New York Annual Report, 1958-1960; 1962-1965 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - State University of New York Annual Report, 1987-1988 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - State University of New York – News, 1969-1971 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - State University of New York: The News, 1971-1973 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - State University of New York: The News, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - State University of New York: The News, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - State University of New York: The News, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - State University of New York: The News, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - State University of New York: The News, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - State University of New York: The News, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - State University of New York: The News, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - State University of New York: The News, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - State University of New York: The News, 1982-1983 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - State University of New York: The News, 1984-1988 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - State University of New York: Washington Report, 1966-1977 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - State University of New York: Washington Report, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - State University of New York: Washington Report, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - State University of New York: Washington Report, 1970-1971; 1973 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - State University of New York: Washington Report, 1974-1977 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Statement on Dr. Robert Ketter – State University at Buffalo, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Statement to Subcommittee on Oversight and Investigations of the Committee on Interstate and Foreign Commerce, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Statements of Stewardship, 1978; Undated (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Structure and Function of Decision-Making Organizations Involved in Campus Governance, Undated (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - SUNY Albany President's Reaffirmation Statement, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - SUNY Budgets, 1974; 1976; 1980; 1982; Undated (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - SUNY Cost Study – Instruction Costs Per Medical Student, 1973-1974; Undated (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - SUNY Downstate Medical College Center Opening Convocation, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - SUNY Public Image, 1978; Undated (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - SUNY/The Arts on Television: A Progress Report, Undated (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Temporary State Commission on the Future of Postsecondary Education, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Testimonies to the Board of Trustees, 1977-1980; Undated (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Time for Leadership and a Time for Opportunity, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Trustee Retreat, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - University Commission on Purposes and Priorities, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - University Planning – Redirection and Response, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - University Religious Studies Programs, 1976-1977 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Vice Chancellor for Research and Graduate Studies Job Description, Undated (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Witness List – Educational Records Hearing, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 29)